{"questions":[

    {"question": "How many chicken are reared for mean each year?", "A": "60 Billion", "B": "55 Billion", "C": "32 Billion", "D": "9 Billion", "Answer": "60 Billion"},
    {"question": "Between 1996 and 2016, by how much did the demand for chicken in India grow ?", "A": "124%", "B": "50%", "C": "95%", "D": "183%", "Answer": "183%"},
    {"question": "A factory farmed chicken lives an avarage of ", "A": "63 days", "B": "15 days", "C": "74 days", "D": "42 days", "Answer": "42 days"},
    {"question": "How many chickens are slaughted every second ?", "A": "5000", "B": "2000", "C": "1000", "D": "500", "Answer": "2000"},
    {"question": "How many grams do factory-grown chickens gain per day ?", "A": "1 gram", "B": "50 grams", "C": "24 grams", "D": "65 grams", "Answer": "50 grams"},
    {"question": "What a chicken's normal lifespan ?", "A": "10-15 years", "B": "2-4 years", "C": "1-2 years", "D": "5-10 years", "Answer": "10-15 years"},
    {"question": "Chickens bred for food are forced to grow how many times faster than they normally would ?", "A": "10 times", "B": "65 times", "C": "72 times", "D": "5 times", "Answer": "65 times"},
    {"question": "Due to their rapid breeding growth, how many chickens experience experience painful leg problems every year globally?", "A": "10,3 Billion", "B": "6,5 Billion", "C": "12,5 Billion", "D": "7,8 Billion", "Answer": "12,5 Billion"},
    {"question": "Which health conditions do factory farmed chickens suffer from ?", "A": "Heart failure", "B": "Hemorrhage", "C": "Lacerations", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "At what rate are chickens killed in a slaughterhouse ?", "A": "10 chickens per minute", "B": "20 chickens per minute", "C": "140 chickens per minute", "D": "70 chickens per minute", "Answer": "140 chickens per minute"},
    {"question": "Chickens have a profound memory, how many faces of their species can they distuguish between ?", "A": "100 faces", "B": "210 faces", "C": "50 faces", "D": "70 faces", "Answer": "200 faces"},
    {"question": "Which of these statements is true ?", "A": "Chickens have pain receptors", "B": "Chickens make friends and grieve their death", "C": "Chickens dream", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "Wild chickens lay around 10 eggs per year while genetically manipulated to lay more than ___ per year.", "A": "50 eggs", "B": "100 eggs", "C": "23 eggs", "D": "300 eggs", "Answer": "300 eggs"},
    {"question": "The overproduction off eggs takes a serious tool on hens' lives. Which of these conditions do they end up suffering from ?", "A": "Osteoporosis", "B": "Tumors", "C": "Uterine Prolapse", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "How many males chicks are killed immediately each year in egg production ?", "A": "100-200 million", "B": "1-2 Billion", "C": "4-6 Billion", "D": "500-700 million", "Answer": "4-6 Billion"},
    {"question": "How many chickens are estimated to be living worldwide ?", "A": "33 Billion", "B": "50 Billion", "C": "10 Billion", "D": "25 Billion", "Answer": "33 Billion"},
    {"question": "Scientific evidence has proven the shared common ancestry between chickens and which dinasour", "A": "Cerapods", "B": "Dilophosaurus", "C": "Tyrannosaurus rex", "D": "Pterodactyl", "Answer": "Tyrannosaurus rex"},
    {"question": "Which colour lights can chicken see ?", "A": "Red", "B": "Blue and Green", "C": "Ultraviolet", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "How many uniques vocalizations do chickens have to communicate ?", "A": "30", "B": "11", "C": "23", "D": "4", "Answer": "30"},
    {"question": "What do chickens cover themselves with to bathe ?", "A": "Dirt", "B": "Water", "C": "Mud", "D": "None of the above", "Answer": "Dirt"},
    {"question": "Which of these statements is true ?", "A": "Chickens have hierarchical flocks", "B": "Chickens can distiguish between one another", "C": "Chicken demonstrate complex problem solving skills", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "Chickens are ___", "A": "Herbivores", "B": "Carnivores", "C": "Omnivores", "D": "None of the above", "Answer": "Omnivores"},
    {"question": "Which of these qualities do chickens have ?", "A": "They have self-control", "B": "They can pass on knowledge", "C": "They can worry", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "How fast can chickens run? ", "A": "14,5 km per hour", "B": "10 km per hour", "C": "5 km per hour", "D": "16 km per hour", "Answer": "14,5 km per hour"},
    {"question": "When do chickens start teaching their chicks?", "A": "Before they hatch ", "B": "Immediately after they hatch", "C": "A few days after they hatch", "D": "Never", "Answer": "Before they hatch"},
    {"question": "Which of these statements is false about chickens?", "A": "They can differentiate between people", "B": "The prefer beautiful people", "C": "They can recognize their keeper", "D": "None of the above", "Answer": "Nove of the above"},
    {"question": "When do chicks start pecking ?", "A": "After 7 days", "B": "After 3 days", "C": "After 14 days", "D": "After 30 days", "Answer": "After 3 days"},
    {"question": "Approximately how many eggs can hens lay per year ?", "A": "35 eggs", "B": "60 eggs", "C": "300 eggs", "D": "137 eggs", "Answer": "300 eggs"},
    {"question": "What is the record number of eggs laid by a chicken in one day? ", "A": "2", "B": "4", "C": "5", "D": "7", "Answer": "7"},
    {"question": "What is the record number of eggs laid by a chicken in one year", "A": "322", "B": "157", "C": "264", "D": "371", "Answer": "371"},
    {"question": "Chicken can taste ___", "A": "Saltiness", "B": "Sweetness", "C": "Both saltiness and sweetness", "D": "Neither saltiness nor sweetness", "Answer": "Saltiness"},
    {"question": "What is the record number of yolks in one egg?", "A": "5", "B": "6", "C": "8", "D": "9", "Answer": "9"},
    {"question": "How much did the largest chicken egg recorded weight ?", "A": "340 grams", "B": "50 grams", "C": "127 grams", "D": "293 grams", "Answer": "340 grams"},
    {"question": "How many days does it take for chicken eggs to incubate and hatch ?", "A": "15 days", "B": "19 days", "C": "21 days", "D": "27 days", "Answer": "21 days"},
    {"question": "Matilda is very well known chicken who was an assistant to magician. How old was Matilda when she died ?", "A": "10 years old", "B": "17 years old", "C": "15 years old", "D": "16 years old", "Answer": "16 years old"},
    {"question": "When chickens listen to classical music, they can lay ___", "A": "Bigger eggs", "B": "Heavier eggs", "C": "Neither A or B", "D": "Both A and B", "Answer": "Both A and B"},
    {"question": "How many eyelids do chicken have ? ", "A": "1 eyelid", "B": "2 eyelids", "C": "3 eyelids", "D": "4 eyelids", "Answer": "3 eyelids"},
    {"question": "Broilers(chickens farmed for meat) are bread to grow ___", "A": "Faster", "B": "Bigger", "C": "Faster and Bigger", "D": "Neither A, B or C", "Answer": "Faster and Bigger"},
    {"question": "Industry farmed chickens often experience injuries and stress due to they ways they are ___", "A": "Handled", "B": "Transported", "C": "Slaughted", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "The air in chicken factory farms can become highly polluted with ammonia from droppings. How does this affect the chickens? ", "A": "Damages their eyes", "B": "Damages their respiratory System", "C": "Burns their legs, chests and feet", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "In factory farms, how much space does each chicken have to move around (Measure using sheet of paper sizes) ? ", "A": "A4", "B": "A3", "C": "A2", "D": "A1", "Answer": "A4"},
    {"question": "Chicken in factory farms often suffer from ___ ", "A": "Chronic hunger", "B": "Stress", "C": "Frustration", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "What were chicken first domesticated for ?", "A": "Cockfights", "B": "Meat", "C": "Eggs", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "Cockfights"},
    {"question": "How long did Mike the headless chicken survive with his head ?", "A": "18 months", "B": "2 months", "C": "7 months", "D": "15 months", "Answer": "18 months"},
    {"question": "As chickens get older they start laying ___ ", "A": "Fewer eggs", "B": "Larger eggs", "C": "Both A and B", "D": "Neither A nor B", "Answer": "Both A and B"},
    {"question": "Chicken use the sun to ___", "A": "Locate food", "B": "Locate water", "C": "Tell the time", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "How many countries do not have chickens ? ", "A": "10 countries", "B": "5 countries", "C": "15 countries", "D": "2 countries", "Answer": "2 countries"},
    {"question": "How long does it take a for a hen to produce an egg ?", "A": "26 hours", "B": "24 hours", "C": "20 hours", "D": "18 hours", "Answer": "26 hours"},
    {"question": "How long did the oldest chicken live ?", "A": "20 years", "B": "17 years", "C": "22 years", "D": "18 years", "Answer": "22 years"},
    {"question": "How many times does a hen turn her eggs per day", "A": "10 times", "B": "50 times", "C": "27 times", "D": "30 times", "Answer": "50 times"},
    {"question": "Which of these statements is true ?", "A": "Female chicken mate with many different males", "B": "Female chickens can choose to eject sperm", "C": "Both A and B", "D": "Neither A nor B", "Answer": "Both A and B"},
    {"question": "Which of these statements is true ?", "A": "Chickens use past experiences to make decisions", "B": "Chickens are hierarchical", "C": "Chickens empathize with their peers", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"},
    {"question": "What are the indications of a sick chicken ? ", "A": "Pale comb", "B": "Lack of appetite", "C": "Reduced egg production", "D": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"}
    


]}